PABLO CEBOLLADA

RENDER PROGRAMMER

CONTACT



paablooch.github.io



Pablo Cebollada Hernández



PaablooCH



paabloo.ch@gmail.com



+34 655 072 165



Barcelona, Spain

SKILLS

Dynamic worker

Compromise

Quick learn capability

Self-confidence

Critical thinking

Problem-solving

Adaptability and flexibility

Strong work ethic

EDUCATION

Master in Advanced Programming for AAA Videogames

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya - UPC BarcelonaTech - Talent School

October 2022 - November 2023

Degree in Computer Science

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya - UPC **BarcelonaTech**

September 2017 - January 2022

PROFILE

I'm a junior programmer, with a strong background in the creation of applications and a passion for graphics programming. My experience includes the development of video games in 2D, with non-commercial engine, and in 3D using Unity, and lately, I have developed the graphics part of an engine for the final master project I coursed, which has allowed me to develop skills using and creating shaders with OpenGL and my understanding and use of the C++ language. I am excited about the opportunity to contribute to your company's success and look forward to discussing how my skills and experience can benefit your team.

RELEVANT PROJECTS

Axolotl Engine

In-house game Engine developed in C++ and OpenGL, for the Master in Advanced Programming for AAA Videogames' final project.



https://github.com/Horizons-Games/Axolotl-Engine

Lego Star Wars: Starfall Rebellion

Game developed in C++ using Axolotl Engine with a Lego Star Wars aesthetic and playability.



https://github.com/Horizons-Games/Axolotl-Engine

Megaman

2D Game developed in C++, with a in-house Engine, based on The Goonies (NES) with a Megaman 7 aesthetic.



https://github.com/PaablooCH/VJ-2D

Undercooked

3D Game developed using Unity, based on the original Overcooked, models were made using MagicaVoxel.



https://github.com/PaablooCH/VJ-3D

Deus Ex Machina

First in-house engine, developed in C++ and OpenGL, for Master in Advanced Programming for AAA Videogames' first milestone.



https://github.com/PaablooCH/Deus-Ex-Machina

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES



C++



C#



OpenGL API



Java

TOOLS





NSight











LANGUAGES

Spanish

Catalan

English

WORK EXPERIENCE

Render & engine Programmer

Horizons Games

January 2023-Present

- For one part, I developed a series of features in the rendering system of the engine, involving the use of multiple shaders with different rendering purposes. Additionally, I worked on features for both the engine and gameplay.
- I also reviewed code written by my teammates..
- Detailed achievements:
 - Good Knowledge of C++ and Render technics.
 - o Good Knowledge about Life Cycle of Game Development.

Software Developer

IThink UPC

February 2022-February 2023

- I was mainly working on two projects. One involved the maintenance of a product management application, which initially began with a team of three people. The second was a property management application, which was developed by a team of nine people.
- Detailed achievements:
 - o Good work in a department with twelve people.
 - o Working with a multidisciplinary team.
 - Utilizing the Scrum methodology with Jira to manage projects.
 - o Ability to effectively communicate with customers.
 - Working with the implementation of various programming patterns.

Software Developer (Internship)

Telespazio Ibérica

April 2021-January 2022

- I was rotating between two teams. One was responsible for application migration, and the other was focused on creating and developing a corporate
- Detailed achievements:
 - o Met all the deadlines set by the client.

INTEREST

The techniques behind games

How companies develop their games, the techniques they employ, and how they implement those techniques, particularly in the graphics department

Videogames' life

Understand the stages a video game goes through from its initial concept, through development to its gold release, and how its life continues post-gold (DLC, expansions, balance changes, etc.).